<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
    <addon id="plugin.video.fenlight" name="Fen Light" provider-name="Tikipeter" version="2.0.07">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
            <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
            <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
            <license />
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/media/fenlight_icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart2.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
            <news>INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="plugin.video.fenlight.patched" name="Fen Light Patched" provider-name="Tikipeter" version="2.0.27">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
            <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
            <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
            <license />
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/media/fenlight_icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart2.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
            <news>[v2.0.27]:
  * Keep the known-good direct player.run(...) foreground playback path on macOS Kodi installs instead of routing playback back through a resolver handoff.
  * Clarify maintainer expectations around subtitle-aware retries so fallback work preserves the current direct playback path and prefers the next best subtitle-backed candidates first.
  * Keep selector shadow validation focused on subtitle-backed ranking versus the actually played source without moving playback policy into the standalone selector.

[v2.0.26]:
  * Ship Fen Light Patched with reuse language invoker disabled by default so repo installs stop re-enabling it for setups that expect it off.

[v2.0.25]:
  * Refresh packaged branding and artwork so repo installs no longer reuse the old selector-test presentation.

[v2.0.24]:
  * Prefer direct subtitle filename evidence over uploader comments when both are available.
  * Strip OpenSubtitles track and language suffixes before source/subtitle matching.

[v2.0.23]:
  * Bundle the subtitle selector inside the add-on instead of depending on an external dev repo path.
  * Build the autoplay retry pool from one title-level subtitle gather and local selector ranking.

INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.kodi.favourites.sync" name="Kodi Favourites Sync" version="0.2.36" provider-name="Codex">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="sync_now.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="pair_google_drive.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Sync Kodi favourites.xml with Google Drive</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">A minimal background service add-on that syncs Kodi favourites.xml with Google Drive using OAuth refresh tokens.</description>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>MIT</license>
            <source>https://example.invalid/service.kodi.favourites.sync</source>
            <news>v0.2.36
- Stop using `datetime.strptime` for Google Drive timestamps so Shield startup sync does not crash while parsing remote modified times

v0.2.35
- Log the full Python traceback for sync failures so intermittent Shield startup errors are diagnosable from Kodi logs

v0.2.34
- Refine the packaged README with the simplified user-facing intro and explicit bridge key-deletion notes

v0.2.33
- Rewrite the packaged README to focus on the OAuth bridge security model and shipped addon behavior

v0.2.32
- Add bridge refresh-secret support so startup token refresh uses a second device secret instead of a public refresh endpoint

v0.2.31
- Replace the add-on fanart with the provided artwork, resized into Kodi's JPEG fanart format

v0.2.30
- Restore hidden internal settings and harden setting reads so Android startup sync does not crash after UI cleanup

v0.2.29
- Simplify the General settings page to only Pair Google Drive now and Sync on Kodi startup

v0.2.28
- Replace the add-on icon with the provided Favourites Sync artwork

v0.2.27
- Move Pair Google Drive to the top of the General settings section for faster setup

v0.2.26
- Remove the visible Remote Storage settings category so normal users stay on the supported appdata sync path

v0.2.25
- Replace blank placeholder artwork with a real add-on icon and fanart for Kodi UI

v0.2.23
- Repackage the last known-good Android behavior from the 0.2.15 code path as a newer update so Kodi can install the stable rollback cleanly

v0.2.22
- Roll back to the pre-experiment sync behavior used before the post-download UI refresh tests on Android

v0.2.21
- Roll back the post-download UI refresh experiment and restore the previously stable sync behavior on Android

v0.2.20
- Harden the download path on Android so a non-callable timestamp or local metadata refresh issue cannot abort a successful remote favourites download

v0.2.19
- Make the post-download skin reload fully non-blocking and switch to the simpler `ReloadSkin` builtin form so download syncs still succeed even if UI refresh is unsupported

v0.2.18
- Retry the post-download skin reload with a defensive builtin check so Android builds that expose no callable builtin API fall back safely

v0.2.17
- Revert the experimental post-download skin reload after it caused a runtime error on Android

v0.2.16
- Try a best-effort Kodi skin reload after downloading a newer remote favourites.xml so favourites may refresh without a second reboot

v0.2.15
- Log the effective upload toggle at sync start so Kodi UI/state mismatches are visible in the log

v0.2.14
- Log the granted OAuth scope string at sync start so Drive app-data scope mismatches are visible in Kodi logs

v0.2.13
- Use Kodi's native string settings API when available so claimed OAuth tokens actually persist on newer builds

v0.2.12
- Add targeted pairing and token persistence logging so Kodi-side OAuth handoff failures are visible in the log

v0.2.11
- Improve QR dialog readability with brighter text, better spacing, and wrapped URL display

v0.2.10
- Bundle a local skin texture for the pairing dialog so the modal background does not depend on Kodi skin assets

v0.2.9
- Make the pairing QR dialog fully opaque so it reads as a proper modal over Kodi settings

v0.2.8
- Add a self-contained pairing dialog background so the QR modal stays readable on Kodi skins without bundled dialog textures

v0.2.7
- Rework the Kodi QR dialog layout using a proven dialog window structure and local QR image file rendering

v0.2.6
- Send the pairing creation request as explicit JSON so the Vercel bridge parses Kodi requests correctly

v0.2.5
- Show a Kodi QR pairing dialog so users can scan the Vercel sign-in link from their phone
- Stop auto-opening the system browser during pairing
- Fix pairing progress updates for Kodi builds that only accept the older DialogProgress signature

v0.2.4
- Route the Google Drive pairing action through RunPlugin for better compatibility on Kodi/macOS
- Add a startup fallback toggle to launch pairing on the next Kodi start if direct triggering is unavailable

v0.2.3
- Add a Kodi settings action button to start Google Drive pairing directly from the add-on UI</news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.a4ksubtitles.patched" name="a4kSubtitles Patched" version="3.23.22" provider-name="Unknown">
        <requires>
            <import addon="script.module.requests" />
            <import addon="vfs.libarchive" optional="true" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="main.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="main_service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en">a4kSubtitles Patched - Multi-Source Subtitles Addon</summary>
            <description>
Multi-source subtitles addon optimized for Seren and a4kScrapers.
Supports: OpenSubtitles, BSPlayer, Podnadpisi.NET, SubDL, Addic7ed
        </description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
            <license>MIT License</license>
            <website>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</website>
            <source>https://github.com/newt-sc/a4kSubtitles</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>icon.png</icon>
                <screenshot>screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
                <screenshot>screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
                <screenshot>screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
            </assets>
            <news>
[v3.23.22]:
  * Refresh stale cached OpenSubtitles rows when translation markers are missing so shadow snapshots and downstream selectors keep ai_translated and machine_translated state.
  * Make API-mode Fenlight probing survive live Kodi builds where xbmc.Player().getPlayingFile is read-only by falling back to mocked a4k video metadata helpers.
  * Add a backward-compatible logger.info(...) alias in the Kodi logger shim so shadow subtitle snapshot logging no longer throws an attribute error.
  * Record the Hoppers follow-up: direct OpenSubtitles API reproduction returns the Dutch SyncUP subtitle with ai_translated=true, while the active live Kodi runtime path still serializes it as false/false and needs more tracing.

[v3.23.21]:
  * Prevent autoplay subtitle preparation from crashing when uploader comments contain Unicode digit separators such as ².
  * Rewrite matching-stem runtime subtitle temp filenames before attach so Kodi shows a readable external subtitle name instead of collapsing to generic (External).

[v3.23.20]:
  * Migrate the Kodi settings dialog to the current schema so provider toggles and account fields no longer reset while switching categories.
  * Restore selector shadow snapshots for multi-provider runs, including paired Fenlight source snapshots and history-only runtime/manual subtitle snapshots.
  * Make manual subtitle picks attach the real downloaded file directly so Kodi shows the chosen release name instead of TempSubtitle, without the old false failed-download notice.

[v3.23.19]:
  * Refresh packaged branding and artwork so repo installs no longer reuse the old selector-test presentation.

[v3.23.18]:
  * Add universal [AI]/[MT] badges to manual search subtitle rows so translated results are clearly marked across skins.

[v3.23.17]:
  * Prefer full OpenSubtitles release names for selector matching.
  * Keep API-mode settings overrides compatible with Kodi's read-only Addon object.
  * Refresh cached rows missing translation flags before selector ranking.

[v3.23.13]:
  * Fix comment-fallback ranking crash in final subtitle selection.

[v3.23.12]:
  * Use OpenSubtitles uploader comments as a fallback-only compatibility signal after direct filename matching.

[v3.23.11]:
  * Demote AI and machine-translated subtitle results during final ranking so they only win as fallback.

[v3.23.10]:
  * Move full release history into CHANGELOG.md so repository metadata stays compact.

[v3.23.9]:
  * Fix OpenSubtitles download retries and cleanup after failed downloads.
  * Improve subtitle ranking for prerelease and release-family mismatches.
  * Add resilient OpenSubtitles movie fallback search when year metadata is wrong.
  * Show a notification when an AI or machine translated subtitle is selected.

Full release history is now tracked in CHANGELOG.md.
        </news>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="skin.arctic.horizon.2.1" name="Arctic Horizon 2.1" provider-name="DeFiNiek" version="0.0.1">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0" />
            <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.4.0" />
            <import addon="script.skinvariables" version="1.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.texturemaker" version="0.2.8" />
            <import addon="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper" version="5.1.11~nexus" />
            <import addon="resource.images.weathericons.white" version="0.0.1" />
            <import addon="resource.images.studios.coloured" version="0.0.1" />
            <import addon="resource.font.robotocjksc" version="0.0.1" />
        </requires>
        <extension debugging="false" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1" point="xbmc.gui.skin">
            <res aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" height="1080" width="1920" />
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en">Minimal. Classic. Gradients. Widgets.</summary>
            <description lang="en">Arctic Horizon 2.1</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share-Alike 4.0</license>
            <forum />
            <source />
            <assets>
                <icon>icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="repository.dutchtech" name="DutchTech Repository" provider-name="DutchTech" version="1.0.42">
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="DutchTech Repository">
            <dir>
                <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TechXXX/kodirepo/main/addons.xml</info>
                <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TechXXX/kodirepo/main/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
                <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/TechXXX/kodirepo/main/zips/</datadir>
            </dir>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary>Repository for DutchTech Kodi add-ons.</summary>
            <description>Install this repository to receive DutchTech Kodi add-on updates from a GitHub Pages-hosted source.</description>
            <disclaimer />
            <platform>all</platform>
            <assets>
                <icon>icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
</addons>
