<addon id="plugin.video.fenlight.patched" name="Fen Light Patched" provider-name="Tikipeter" version="2.0.29">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
        <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <license/>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/fenlight_icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart2.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>[v2.0.29]:
  * Promote the selector runtime handoff build to the main repo with smoother autoplay dialog closing and direct source-specific subtitle attachment.
  * Keep fullscreen-first resolver cleanup so playback start no longer flashes back to the skin start screen during successful autoplay.
  * Preserve selector-chosen source/subtitle pairings into runtime playback instead of falling back to a generic runtime subtitle search.

[v2.0.28]:
  * Keep the smoother autoplay handoff that waits for fullscreen before closing the resolver window, reducing the flash back to the skin start screen.
  * Bridge selector playback metadata into Kodi properties so patched a4k can consume the exact selector-chosen subtitle for the active source at runtime.
  * Trim the successful pre-player settle before player.run(...) to reduce startup latency without changing retry timing.

[v2.0.26]:
  * Ship Fen Light Patched with reuse language invoker disabled by default so repo installs stop re-enabling it for setups that expect it off.

[v2.0.25]:
  * Refresh packaged branding and artwork so repo installs no longer reuse the old selector-test presentation.

[v2.0.24]:
  * Prefer direct subtitle filename evidence over uploader comments when both are available.
  * Strip OpenSubtitles track and language suffixes before source/subtitle matching.

[v2.0.23]:
  * Bundle the subtitle selector inside the add-on instead of depending on an external dev repo path.
  * Build the autoplay retry pool from one title-level subtitle gather and local selector ranking.

INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
