<addon id="plugin.video.fenlight.patched" name="Fen Light Patched" provider-name="Tikipeter" version="2.0.36">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
        <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <license/>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/fenlight_icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart2.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>[v2.0.36]:
  * Add support for up to three Gemini API keys with automatic fallback on rate-limit or quota-exhaustion responses.
  * Expand the subtitle-backed retry pool to the best 10 selector-ranked candidates and let subtitle comments promote a stronger alias for the same subtitle item when they improve the release match.

[v2.0.35]:
  * Teach Gemini intent parsing to preserve named people separately from generic keywords so movie AI searches can feed TMDb cast-aware discovery and better title-like prompt handling.

[v2.0.34]:
  * Preserve meaningful technical bracket segments during bundled subtitle-selector normalization so release matching keeps cues like [1080p], codec tags, and year-style bracket tokens instead of discarding them as noise.

[v2.0.33]:
  * Add TMDb collection-search support for movie searches so matching collection results can open directly into the related movie-set listing.

[v2.0.32]:
  * Republish the same Gemini-backed AI Search test build under a higher test-only version so Kodi updates cleanly from the current production 2.0.31 release.

[v2.0.31]:
  * Add Gemini-backed AI Search inside Fen Light Patched so natural-language discovery can build TMDb-backed movie and TV result lists without leaving the patched addon.
  * Store AI Search history locally and expose a Gemini API key field in the existing settings manager.

[v2.0.30]:
  * Clear local Kodi bookmark rows using the real plugin:// playback URLs so erase-bookmark actions target the active movie or episode instead of relying on the old broad filename match.

[v2.0.28]:
  * Keep the smoother autoplay handoff that waits for fullscreen before closing the resolver window, reducing the flash back to the skin start screen.
  * Bridge selector playback metadata into Kodi properties so patched a4k can consume the exact selector-chosen subtitle for the active source at runtime.
  * Trim the successful pre-player settle before player.run(...) to reduce startup latency without changing retry timing.

[v2.0.26]:
  * Ship Fen Light Patched with reuse language invoker disabled by default so repo installs stop re-enabling it for setups that expect it off.

[v2.0.25]:
  * Refresh packaged branding and artwork so repo installs no longer reuse the old selector-test presentation.

[v2.0.24]:
  * Prefer direct subtitle filename evidence over uploader comments when both are available.
  * Strip OpenSubtitles track and language suffixes before source/subtitle matching.

[v2.0.23]:
  * Bundle the subtitle selector inside the add-on instead of depending on an external dev repo path.
  * Build the autoplay retry pool from one title-level subtitle gather and local selector ranking.

INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
