<addon id="plugin.video.fenlight.patched" name="Fen Light Patched" provider-name="DutchTech" version="2.0.72">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.19.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/fenlight.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">Access your content from Easynews and Debrid Clouds.</summary>
        <description lang="en">This add-on is intended for advanced Kodi users only. You must own the content of any media you play through this addon. This is an English language only add-on.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon does not host any of the content which is found and has no affiliation with any of the content providers.</disclaimer>
        <license/>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/media/baslite_icon_blue.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/media/fenlight_fanart2.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>[v2.0.72]:
  * Polish TorBox Usenet Search source display as TB USENET/NZB instead of prefixing release titles.
  * Keep TorBox Usenet Search rows mixed into normal quality and size sorting instead of pinning them with TorBox cloud sort-to-top.

[v2.0.71]:
  * Pass Fen Light's TMDb/show IDs into the a4k subtitle retry pool so OpenSubtitles can use exact parent-ID episode searches and avoid broad title fallbacks.
  * Add TorBox Usenet Search controls for movies and TV shows, plus automatic no-results retry support for cached TorBox Usenet Search.

[v2.0.70]:
  * Validate TorBox Web Download playback and remove temporary scrape/resolver diagnostics while keeping the WebDL cloud fix.

[v2.0.69]:
  * Add TorBox Web Download cloud support so hoster uploads such as GoFile-backed items appear in TorBox cloud scraping, browsing, resolving, and deleting alongside torrent and usenet items.

[v2.0.68]:
  * Seed first-run settings from the live patched Fen Light profile, including CocoScrapers, list/result/playback preferences, size filters, pagination, and update behavior while leaving user credentials, tokens, account values, and local paths out of the package.

[v2.0.67]:
  * Refresh the Trakt and Real-Debrid QR-backed device-auth flow with styled Trakt QR cards, direct activation QR targets where available, and the latest patched TMDb Helper Trakt QR dialog support.

[v2.0.66]:
  * Add an optional strict original-language AI Search filter so prompts like Korean, German, or Dutch can become TMDb original-language constraints instead of loose keywords when enabled.

[v2.0.65]:
  * Guard Trakt re-authorization prompts so only one dialog appears at a time, and skip watched-indicator refresh when Trakt returns an invalid payload instead of trying to thread over bad data.

[v2.0.64]:
  * Force Extras trailer playback into fullscreen video and stop the trailer when Back leaves fullscreen playback.

[v2.0.63]:
  * In Extras, fetch TMDb's standalone videos list when localized metadata has no trailers so Dutch metadata can still play English YouTube trailers.

[v2.0.62]:
  * Prefer playable YouTube trailer keys in the extras window, fall back to the best sorted YouTube trailer when raw trailer metadata is missing or non-plugin, and show a clearer no-trailer notice instead of failing playback.

[v2.0.61]:
  * Add a final OpenSubtitles English AI-translation fallback after Dutch subtitle matching fails, and tighten episodic subtitle matching so unrelated S01E01 Dutch results cannot win on generic release tags.

[v2.0.60]:
  * Use stable Trakt list IDs for custom/user list browsing, pagination, cache keys, like/unlike, and owned-list edits, with legacy slug fallback for old shortcuts and widgets.

[v2.0.59]:
  * Update the bundled default Trakt client ID and secret, and keep the settings manager restore-default actions aligned with the new Trakt defaults.

[v2.0.57]:
  * Refresh a stale Trakt access token once with the stored refresh token before showing the re-authentication prompt, and avoid caching invalid Trakt activity payloads.
  * Restore a dedicated in-play next-episode jump from the OSD while keeping Stop behavior available for episode playback.

[v2.0.52]:
  * Fix local resume bookmark cleanup after playback stop, including newer Kodi video-database detection and safer bookmark clearing around the patched playback flow.

[v2.0.50]:
  * Add a bundled default OMDb API key so patched Fenlight ships with extra-ratings support enabled without manual OMDb key entry.

[v2.0.48]:
  * Update the built-in default TMDb API key and keep the Restore Default TMDb API Key action aligned with the new bundled value.

[v2.0.47]:
  * Roll back the stricter playback-start validation from 2.0.46 and republish the prior startup behavior under a higher version so Kodi updates away from the bad test build cleanly.

[v2.0.46]:
  * Tighten playback-start validation so a source that only reaches a half-started state gets about 5 seconds of main startup plus a short grace settle before Fen retries the next candidate instead of treating started playback as automatically successful.
  * Keep the current hybrid handoff, and note that an intermittent Real-Debrid/Kodi teardown hang after stop() is still under investigation when a bad stream refuses to close quickly.

[v2.0.45]:
  * Strip tracker suffix noise like .rartv. and .eztv before release-group matching so season-pack sources such as S01 BiRDHOUSE rank above weaker same-quality fallbacks when their episode subtitle release matches.

[v2.0.44]:
  * Skip autoplay sources only when every detected audio stream is a blocked pirate-language track, so bad metadata cannot allow Russian-only/Chinese-only/Ukrainian-only sources and mixed-language sources with an acceptable track can still play.

[v2.0.43]:
  * Use the show's original or English title plus the actual episode name when building TV subtitle-search metadata and filenames, reducing mismatches on localized show labels.

[v2.0.42]:
  * Skip autoplay sources whose detected audio streams are Russian-only, Ukrainian-only, or Chinese-only unless the selected title metadata already expects that spoken language.

[v2.0.41]:
  * Add an explicit Trakt authorization status row to the settings window so expired or incomplete auth is visible even when a stale username is still stored.
  * Only show Authorize when Trakt is not fully authorized and keep Revoke tied to a stored Trakt user instead of treating the username as the only auth signal.

[v2.0.40]:
  * Demote bare generic movie-title subtitles to low-confidence fallbacks so structured release-specific matches can win when available.
  * Demote low-information source containment hits against structured DVDRip-style subtitles so malformed or ambiguous source names stop outranking stronger higher-quality matches.

[v2.0.39]:
  * Republished the TMDb metadata language and fallback-language controls under a higher production-safe test version.

[v2.0.38]:
  * Add TMDb metadata language and fallback-language settings for movie, TV, collection, episode, and people details.
  * Fill missing summaries from the configured fallback language instead of dropping back to English-only metadata requests.

[v2.0.37]:
  * Rebrand the patched add-on metadata under DutchTech so Kodi listings no longer show the upstream provider name for this repo build.

[v2.0.36]:
  * Add support for up to three Gemini API keys with automatic fallback on rate-limit or quota-exhaustion responses.
  * Expand the subtitle-backed retry pool to the best 10 selector-ranked candidates and let subtitle comments promote a stronger alias for the same subtitle item when they improve the release match.

[v2.0.35]:
  * Teach Gemini intent parsing to preserve named people separately from generic keywords so movie AI searches can feed TMDb cast-aware discovery and better title-like prompt handling.

[v2.0.34]:
  * Preserve meaningful technical bracket segments during bundled subtitle-selector normalization so release matching keeps cues like [1080p], codec tags, and year-style bracket tokens instead of discarding them as noise.

[v2.0.33]:
  * Add TMDb collection-search support for movie searches so matching collection results can open directly into the related movie-set listing.

[v2.0.32]:
  * Republish the same Gemini-backed AI Search test build under a higher test-only version so Kodi updates cleanly from the current production 2.0.31 release.

[v2.0.31]:
  * Add Gemini-backed AI Search inside Fen Light Patched so natural-language discovery can build TMDb-backed movie and TV result lists without leaving the patched addon.
  * Store AI Search history locally and expose a Gemini API key field in the existing settings manager.

[v2.0.30]:
  * Clear local Kodi bookmark rows using the real plugin:// playback URLs so erase-bookmark actions target the active movie or episode instead of relying on the old broad filename match.

[v2.0.28]:
  * Keep the smoother autoplay handoff that waits for fullscreen before closing the resolver window, reducing the flash back to the skin start screen.
  * Bridge selector playback metadata into Kodi properties so patched a4k can consume the exact selector-chosen subtitle for the active source at runtime.
  * Trim the successful pre-player settle before player.run(...) to reduce startup latency without changing retry timing.

[v2.0.26]:
  * Ship Fen Light Patched with reuse language invoker disabled by default so repo installs stop re-enabling it for setups that expect it off.

[v2.0.25]:
  * Refresh packaged branding and artwork so repo installs no longer reuse the old selector-test presentation.

[v2.0.24]:
  * Prefer direct subtitle filename evidence over uploader comments when both are available.
  * Strip OpenSubtitles track and language suffixes before source/subtitle matching.

[v2.0.23]:
  * Bundle the subtitle selector inside the add-on instead of depending on an external dev repo path.
  * Build the autoplay retry pool from one title-level subtitle gather and local selector ranking.

INFO: For latest changes see Changelog within Tools of add-on.</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
